Guide to the Argus Archives Records
Argus Archives Records
- Organizational Files, 1914, 1932-1994; 1914 1994; 63 linear feet
  - DS - The Donkey Sanctuary: P2- Pamphlets, 1980s (Box 1.032, Folder 9)
  - DS - The Donkey Sanctuary: P3- Poster; P4- Bulletins, 1984, 1989-1992 (Box 1.032, Folder 10)
  - DS - The Donkey Sanctuary: P5- Lesson plan; P6- List of welfare offices, 1980s (Box 1.032, Folder 11)
  - DU - DuPont Company: P1- Brochures relating to Halon 1301 toxicology; P2 - Advertisements, 1975, 1991 (Box 1.032, Folder 12)
  - DW - Defenders of Wildlife: P1- Pamphlets, 1975, 1978, 1987 (Box 1.032, Folder 13)
  - DW - Defenders of Wildlife: P2- Bulletins, 1970, 1977-1978, 1981, 1983, 1988, 1991-1992 (Box 1.032, Folder 14)
  - DW - Defenders of Wildlife: P3- Catalog of merchandise; P4- Correspondence, 1979 (Box 1.032, Folder 15)
  - DW - Defenders of Wildlife: P5- Published articles, 1974-1975, 1977-1978, 1982, 1988 (Box 1.032, Folder 16)
  - DW - Defenders of Wildlife: P6- Educational supplement; P7- Statement of Toby Cooper, 1975, 1976, 1978 (Box 1.032, Folder 17)
  - DW - Defenders of Wildlife: P8- Annual report; P9- Indices, 1970-1971, 1977 (Box 1.032, Folder 18)
  - EA - European Alliance (EA): P1- Program (language French); P2- Correspondence (Language English), 1989, 1990 (Box 1.032, Folder 19)
  - EAS - Elmsford Animal Shelter: P1- Bulletins, 1982-1983, 1988-1989 (Box 1.032, Folder 20)
  - EC - European Community: P1- Pamphlets, 1989 (Box 1.032, Folder 21)
  - EC - European Community: P2- Bulletins, 1985-1986, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 1.032, Folder 22)
  - EC - European Community: P3- Newsletter, 1989 (Box 1.032, Folder 23)
  - EC - European Community: P4- Correspondence, 1985-1986, 1988-1990 (Box 1.032, Folder 24)
  - EC - European Community: P5- Publications relating to European Community, 1980, 1989 (Box 1.033, Folder 1)
  - EC - European Community: P6- Magazine, Europe, 1989 (Box 1.033, Folder 2)
  - EC - European Community: P7- Published articles, 1986, 1988, 1990 (Box 1.033, Folder 3)
  - EC - European Community: P8- Report presented by the Commission of the European Community, Draft Report of the European Parliament- Committee on the Environment, Public Health and Consumer Protection, 1985, 1988 (Box 1.033, Folder 4)
  - EC - European Community: P9- Proposals, 1981, 1989 (Box 1.033, Folder 5)
  - EC - European Community: P10- Minutes of Intergroup for Animal Welfare meetings, 1986-1988 (Box 1.033, Folder 6)
  - EC - European Community: P11- Legislation, 1986 (Box 1.033, Folder 7)
  - EC - European Community: P12- Directory of documents, 1986 (Box 1.033, Folder 8)
  - EC - European Community: P13 Handwritten notes, 1993 (Box 1.033, Folder 9)
  - EACC - Educators Care About Animals: P1- Printed matter, 1970s (Box 1.033, Folder 10)
  - EACC - Educators Care About Animals: P2- Bulletins, 1975-1977 (Box 1.033, Folder 11)
  - EACC - Educators Care About Animals: P3-Correspondence, 1975-1976, 1978 (Box 1.033, Folder 12)
  - EACC - Educators Care About Animals: P4- Published articles, 1975-1976 (Box 1.033, Folder 13)
  - EACC - Educators Care About Animals: P5- Curriculum, 1976 (Box 1.033, Folder 14)
  - EACC - Educators Care About Animals: P6- Play scripts, 1970s (Box 1.033, Folder 15)
  - EACC - Educators Care About Animals: P7- Memoranda, 1977 (Box 1.033, Folder 16)
  - ECO - EcoNews: P1- Program listings; P2- Printed matter, 1987, 1989 (Box 1.033, Folder 17)
  - EDF - Environmental Defense Fund: P1- Bulletins, 1986 (Box 1.033, Folder 18)
  - ECSPCA - Erie County Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals: P1- Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1.033, Folder 19)
  - EII - Earth Island Institute: P1- Pamphlets 1988-1989; P2- Bulletins 1988-1989, 1993 (Box 1.033, Folder 20)
  - EEI - Earth Island Institute: P3- Reports; P4- Newsletter, 1980, 1989 (Box 1.033, Folder 21)
  - EF - Earth First: P1- Printed matter; P2- Bulletins; P3- Published articles, 1988-1990 (Box 1.034, Folder 1)
  - EGF - Earth Green Federation: P1- Newsletter; P2- Bulletin; P3- Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 1.034, Folder 2)
  - EI - Eppley Institute: P1- congressional Record Clipping, News clippings, 1977, 1978 (Box 1.034, Folder 3)
  - ELSA - Elsa Wild Animal Appeal: P1- Newsletter, 1988 (Box 1.034, Folder 5)
  - ENDO - Endo Laboratories: P1- Typed and handwritten notes, 1973 (Box 1.034, Folder 6)
  - ERC - Educational Research Council: P1- Published article, 1970 (Box 1.034, Folder 7)
  - EW - Earthwatch: P1- Correspondence; P2- Brochure of excursions; P3- Publication; P4- Poster, 1978, 1982-1983 (Box 1.034, Folder 8)
  - EWB - Edward W. Bourne Behavioral research Laboratory: P1- Handwritten notes, 1973 (Box 1.034, Folder 9)
  - FA - Focus on Animals: P1- Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1.034, Folder 10)
  - FA - Focus on Animals: P2- Miscellaneous publications (Pamphlets, Newsletters, Catalog of Films), 1987-1991 (Box 1.034, Folder 11)
  - FA - Focus on Animals: P3- Article of Incorporation, 1983, 1986, 1991 (Box 1.034, Folder 12)
  - FAACE - Fight Against Animal Cruelty in Europe: P1- Miscellaneous publications (Pamphlets, Bulletins, Newsletters), 1987-1991 (Box 1.034, Folder 13)
  - FAACE - Fight Against Animal Cruelty in Europe: P2- Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 1.034, Folder 14)
  - FAACE - Fight Against Animal Cruelty in Europe: P3- Published articles, 1988-1992 (Box 1.034, Folder 15)
  - FAACE - Fight Against Animal Cruelty in Europe: P4- Reports, 1987, 1989-1990 (Box 1.034, Folder 16)
  - FAACE - Fight Against Animal Cruelty in Europe: P5- Handwritten notes, 1989 (Box 1.034, Folder 17)
  - FAACE - Fight Against Animal Cruelty in Europe: P6- Photographic prints (color), Spain, four animal killed after two hours and ten minutes of torture, bulls, goats, chickens, circa 1989 (Box 1.034, Folder 18)
  - FAACE - Fight Against Animal Cruelty in Europe: P7- Artifact (button), "Blood Fiesta" The Pain in Spain, 1992 (Box 1.034, Folder 19)
  - FACT - Food Animal Concerns Trust: P1- Newsletters, Press releases, 1982-1988 (Box 1.035, Folder 1)
  - FACT - Food Animal Concerns Trust: P2- Bulletins "Fact Sheet" Numbers 1 - 65, 1982-1986 (Box 1.035, Folder 2)
  - FACT - Food Animal Concerns Trust: P3- Correspondence, 1982-1984, 1987-1988 (Box 1.035, Folder 3)
  - FACT - Food Animal Concerns Trust: P4- News clippings, Published articles, 1982-1986, 1993 (Box 1.035, Folder 4)
  - FACT - Food Animal Concerns Trust: P5- Reports, 1983 (Box 1.035, Folder 5)
  - FACT - Food Animal Concerns Trust: P6- Annual reports, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 1.035, Folder 6)
  - FAI - Fur Takers of America International: P1- Publication, 1975 (Box 1.035, Folder 7)
  - FAMA - Fundación Para Los Animales Mexico-America: P1- Newsletters; P2- Correspondence;P3- Published article; P4- Handwritten notes, 1989-1991 (Box 1.035, Folder 8)
  - FARM - Farm Animal Reform Movement: P1- Pamphlets; P2- Newsletters; P3- News clippings, 1982-1990 (Box 1.035, Folder 9)
  - FAS - Federation of American Scientists: P1- F.A.S. Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 1.035, Folder 10)
  - FAS - Federation of American Scientists: P2- Correspondence; P3- Published article, 1977 (Box 1.035, Folder 11)
  - FB - Friends of Beaversprite: P1- Newsletters, News clippings, 1988-1989, 1992 (Box 1.035, Folder 12)
  - FDB - Fur Bearer Defenders: P1- Pamphlets, Newsletters, Bumper-stickers, 1990-1992 (Box 1.035, Folder 13)
  - FDB - Fur Beaver Defenders: P2- Correspondence; P3- Published articles, 1989, 1991 (Box 1.035, Folder 14)
  - FBR - Foundation for Biomedical Research: P1- Publications, 1990, 1992 (Box 1.035, Folder 15)
  - FBR - Foundation for Biomedical Research: P2- Correspondence; P3- Newsletter, Published article, 1988, 1989, 1991 (Box 1.035, Folder 16)
  - FDT - Fieldstone Dog Training: P1- Bulletins and advertisements, 1991-1992 (Box 1.035, Folder 17)
  - FE - Friends of the Earth: P1- Pamphlet, Newsletters, 1988-1994 (Box 1.035, Folder 18)
  - FEE - Foundation for Environmental Education: P1- Correspondence; P2- News clippings, 1972 (Box 1.035, Folder 19)
  - FF - Fragrance Foundation: P1- Correspondence 1973; P2- Published article; P3- Reports, 1973, 1987 (Box 1.035, Folder 20)
  - FAA - Fund For Animals Inc.: P1- Pamphlets, Bulletins, Newsletters, 1979-1981, 1988-1991 (Box 1.036, Folder 1)
  - FAA - Fund For Animals Inc.: P2- Newsletters, 1969-1978 (Box 1.036, Folder 2)
  - FAA - Fund For Animals Inc.: P3- Correspondence, 1974-1976, 1978, 1979, 1982-1983 (Box 1.036, Folder 3)
  - FAA - Fund For Animals Inc.: P4- Published articles, 1975-1976, 1981-1984, 1986-1988 (Box 1.036, Folder 4)
  - FAA - Fund For Animals Inc.: P5- Campaign materials, 1982 (Box 1.036, Folder 5)
  - FAA - Fund For Animals Inc.: P6- Humane Education Catalog, 1983 (Box 1.036, Folder 6)
  - FAA - Fund For Animals Inc.: P7- Humane Education Catalog, 1977 (Box 1.036, Folder 7)
  - FAA - Fund For Animals Inc.: P8- Humane Education Catalog, 1977 (Box 1.036, Folder 8)
  - FAA - Fund For Animals Inc.: P9- Humane Education Catalog, Teaching aids, 1976 (Box 1.036, Folder 9)
  - FAA - Fund For Animals Inc.: P10- Humane Education Catalog, Teaching aids, 1975 (Box 1.036, Folder 10)
  - FGF - Florida Game and Fresh Water Fish Commission: P1- Regulations Summary, 1979-1980 (Box 1.037, Folder 1)
  - FOA - Friends of Animals Inc.: P1- Miscellaneous publications (Pamphlets, Newsletters, Bulletins), 1975-1991 (Box 1.037, Folder 2)
  - FOA - Friends of Animals Inc.: P1- Miscellaneous publications (Pamphlets, Newsletters, Bulletins), 1975-1991 (Box 1.037, Folder 3)
  - FOA - Friends of Animals Inc.: P2- Miscellaneous publications (Newsletters, legislation, statements, published articles), 1970-1984 (Box 1.037, Folder 4)
  - FOA - Friends of Animals Inc.: P3- Correspondence, 1969, 1974, 1981-1982, 1988 (Box 1.037, Folder 5)
  - FOA - Friends of Animals Inc.: P4- Published articles, 1970-1972, 1980-1982, 1988, 1990 (Box 1.037, Folder 6)
  - FOA - Friends of Animals Inc.: P5- Report, 1987 (Box 1.037, Folder 7)
  - FOA - Friends of Animals Inc.: P6- Annual reports, 1968, 1970-1973 (Box 1.037, Folder 8)
  - FOA - Friends of Animals Inc.: P7- Compilation of: Letters to the Editor, Public Service Announcements, and General Publicity. A How to Guide, 1970s (Box 1.037, Folder 9)
  - FOS - Friends of the Sea Otter: P1- Newsletter, 1973 (Box 1.037, Folder 10)
  - FPCI - Federal Provincial Committee for Humane Trapping: P1- Newsletters, 1976 - 1977 (Box 1.037, Folder 11)
  - FP - Fortunate Pet: P1- Pamphlet, Customer Information, Advertisement; P2- Correspondence, 1979 (Box 1.037, Folder 12)
  - FRAME - Fund for Replacement of Animals in Medical Experiments: P1- Pamphlets, 1983, 1988, 1990 (Box 1.038, Folder 1)
  - FRAME - Fund for Replacement of Animals in Medical Experiments: P1- Pamphlets, 1972 - 1977 (Box 1.038, Folder 2)
  - FRAME - Fund for Replacement of Animals in Medical Experiments: P1- Pamphlets, 1969 - 1971 (Box 1.038, Folder 3)
  - FRAME - Fund for Replacement of Animals in Medical Experiments: P2- Newsletters, Progress reports, 1975 - 1983 (Box 1.038, Folder 4)
  - FRAME - Fund for Replacement of Animals in Medical Experiments: P2- Technical report, Progress reports, ATLA Abstracts, 1969 - 1975 (Box 1.038, Folder 5)
  - FRAME - Fund for Replacement of Animals in Medical Experiments: P3- Publications, ATLA abstracts, News releases, 1970 - 1991 (Box 1.038, Folder 6)
  - FRAME - Fund for Replacement of Animals in Medical Experiments: P4- Correspondence, 1970-1977, 1979, 1980, 1983 (Box 1.038, Folder 7)
  - FRAME - Fund for Replacement of Animals in Medical Experiments: P5- Published articles, News clippings, 1970 -1974, 1977 - 1978 (Box 1.038, Folder 8)
  - FRAME - Fund for Replacement of Animals in Medical Experiments: P6- Reports, 1974, 1978 (Box 1.038, Folder 9)
  - FRAME - Fund for Replacement of Animals in Medical Experiments: P7- Invoices, Financial reports, 1970 - 1982 (Box 1.038, Folder 10)
  - FRE - Free, Ann Cottrell: P1- Correspondence, P2- Published articles, 1971, 1973-1974, 1977 - 1978 (Box 1.038, Folder 11)
  - FS - Farm Sanctuary: P1- Pamphlets, Newsletters, 1986 - 1992 (Box 1.038, Folder 12)
  - FS - Farm Sanctuary: P1- Gift catalogs, 1990 - 1991 (Box 1.038, Folder 13)
  - FS - Farm Sanctuary: P2- Correspondence, 1986 - 1988 (Box 1.038, Folder 14)
  - FS - Farm Sanctuary: P3- News clippings, 1986 - 1987 (Box 1.038, Folder 15)
  - FW - Friends of Washoe: P1- publication relating to unwanted chimpanzees, 1982, 1984, 1986 (Box 1.038, Folder 16)
  - FW - Friends of Washoe: P2- Correspondence, 1983, 1985 (Box 1.038, Folder 17)
  - FW - Friends of Washoe: P3- Published articles, 1982, 1984 (Box 1.038, Folder 18)
  - GAPP - Great Ape Protection Project: P1- Pamphlet, P2- Correspondence, 1975 (Box 1.039, Folder 1)
  - GC - Green Cross, Finland: P1- Miscellaneous publication, P2 -Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1.039, Folder 2)
  - GCFC - Green Chimneys Farm Center: P1- Pamphlets, 1970s (Box 1.039, Folder 3)
  - GDF - Geraldine R. Dodge Foundation: P1- Annual reports, 1990 - 1991 (Box 1.039, Folder 4)
  - GDF - Geraldine R. Dodge Foundation: P1- Annual reports, 1982, 1989 (Box 1.039, Folder 5)
  - GDF - Geraldine R. Dodge Foundation: P2- Annual reports, 1978, 1981 (Box 1.039, Folder 6)
  - GDF - Geraldine R. Dodge Foundation: P3- News clipping, 1990 (Box 1.039, Folder 7)
  - GDN - Georgia Department of Natural Resources: P1- Regulations, Trappers report, 1974, 1977 (Box 1.039, Folder 8)
  - GDRC - Gaines Dog Research Center: P1- Publications relating to dog adoption and care, 1969, 1978, 1982 (Box 1.039, Folder 9)
  - GDRC - Gaines Dog Research Center: P1- Publications relating to dog and puppy care, 1969, 1978, 1982 (Box 1.039, Folder 10)
  - GDRC - Gaines Dog Research Center: P1- Publications relating to dogs in society and kennel care, 1969, 1981 (Box 1.039, Folder 11)
  - GDRC - Gaines Dog Research Center: P2- Correspondence, 1981 - 1982 (Box 1.039, Folder 12)
  - GDRC - Gaines Dog Research Center: P3- News clipping, 1981 (Box 1.039, Folder 13)
  - GECA - General Election Coordinating Committee for Animal Protection: P1- Publication; P2- News clipping, 1978, 1979 (Box 1.039, Folder 14)
  - GF - Greyhound Friends: P1- Publications; P2- News clipping, 1988 (Box 1.039, Folder 15)
  - GF - Gorilla Foundation: P1- Miscellaneous publications (pamphlets, newsletters, gorilla posters), P2- Correspondence, 1982 - 1992, 1981, 1983 - 1984 (Box 1.039, Folder 16)
  - GIL - Gillen, Dee: P1- Correspondence, P2- Published articles, 1979 - 1981 (Box 1.039, Folder 17)
  - GLHS - Grandin Livestock Handling System Inc.: P1- Publication, P2- Correspondence, 1970s (Box 1.039, Folder 18)
  - GMC - General Motors Corporation: P1- Correspondence, Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 1.039, Folder 19)
  - GMEL - Gillette Medical Evaluation Laboratories: P1- correspondence, P2- News clipping; P3- Reports, 1972, 1977, 1979, 1987 (Box 1.039, Folder 20)
  - GP - Greenpeace: P1- Bulletins, Decals and stamps, 1988 - 1993 (Box 1.04, Folder 1)
  - GP - Greenpeace: P1- Catalogs, 1990 - 1992 (Box 1.04, Folder 2)
  - GP - Greenpeace: P2- Miscellaneous Publications (bulletins, newsletters, pamphlets), 1982 - 1987 (Box 1.04, Folder 3)
  - GP - Greenpeace: P3- News clippings, 1978, 1979, 1982, 1985 (Box 1.04, Folder 4)
  - GP - Greenpeace: P4- Blueprints of Rainbow Warrior Ship, circa 1985 (Box 1.04, Folder 5)
  - GPO - Government Printing Office: P1- Pamphlet, Catalog of publications, order form, 1974 (Box 1.04, Folder 6)
  - GS - Gellman Sciences: P1- Calendar, 1989 - 1990 (Box 1.04, Folder 7)
  - GSA - Girl Scouts of America: P1- Publication American Girl, 1975 March (Box 1.04, Folder 8)
  - GSA - Girl Scouts of America: P2- Correspondence, 1974 -1975 (Box 1.04, Folder 9)
  - GSAS - Good Shepherd Animal Shelter: P1- Pamphlet, bulletins, 1982, 1985 (Box 1.04, Folder 10)
  - GSAS - Good Shepherd Animal Shelter: P1- Publication The Maverick Nun, 1975 (Box 1.04, Folder 11)
  - GSAS - Good Shepherd Animal Shelter: P2- Published articles, P3- Handwritten note, 1978, 1980, 1982, 1989 (Box 1.04, Folder 12)
  - GSF - Good Shepherd Foundation: P1- Miscellaneous publications (pamphlets, calendars, newsletters, bulletins), 1971, 1972, 1979, 1983 - 1990 (Box 1.04, Folder 13)
  - GSHCAB - Group for the Study of the Human Companion Animal Bond: P1- Newsletter, bulletin, P2- Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 1.04, Folder 14)
  - GSRC - Gombe Stream research center: P1- Correspondence, P2- Published article, 1984, 1987 (Box 1.04, Folder 15)
  - HAS - Hampton Animal Shelter: P1- News clippings, 1975, 1976, 1978, 1979, 1984 (Box 1.041, Folder 1)
  - HAS - Hampton Animal Shelter: P2- Legislation; P3- Card catalog records, P4- Correspondence, 1978, 1984, undated (Box 1.041, Folder 2)
  - HC - Humane Causes Inc.: P1- Pamphlets, bulletins, P2- Correspondence, 1975, 1976, 1978, 1980 - 1981 (Box 1.041, Folder 3)
  - HC - Humane Causes Inc.: P3- Reports, 1976, 1979 (Box 1.041, Folder 4)
  - HC - Humane Causes Inc.: P3- Reports, 1975 (Box 1.041, Folder 5)
  - HC - Humane Causes Inc.: P3- Reports, 1968, 1970 (Box 1.041, Folder 6)
  - HDL - Hawaii Department of Land and Natural Resources: P1- Legislation, P2- Correspondence, 1975, 1980 (Box 1.041, Folder 7)
  - HECO - Humane Education Committee: P1- Newsletters, 1990 - 1992 (Box 1.041, Folder 8)
  - HECO - Humane Education Committee: P1- Pamphlets and bulletins, 1986 - 1991 (Box 1.041, Folder 9)
  - HECO - Humane Education Committee: P2- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 1.041, Folder 10)
  - HED - Hearing Dog Inc.: P1- Miscellaneous Publications (pamphlets, bulletin, newsletter), 1980, 1986, 1990 (Box 1.041, Folder 11)
  - HELP - Humane Enforcement and Legal Protection for Animals: P1- Newsletters, P2- Correspondence, 1986, 1987, 1990, 1991 (Box 1.041, Folder 12)
  - HELP - Humane Enforcement and Legal Protection for Animals: P3- Published articles, 1980 - 1990 (Box 1.041, Folder 13)
  - HELP - Humane Enforcement and Legal Protection for Animals: P4- Publications, 1975 - 1982, 1988 (Box 1.041, Folder 14)
  - HELP - Humane Enforcement and Legal Protection for Animals: P5- Articles of Incorporation, P6- Resume, 1985, 1990 (Box 1.041, Folder 15)
  - HEN - Humane Education Network: P1- bulletins (undated), P2- Handwritten note, 1991 (Box 1.041, Folder 16)
  - HFA - Humane Farming Association: P1- Newsletters, 1988 - 1989, 1991 - 1993 (Box 1.041, Folder 17)
  - HFA - Humane Farming Association: P1- Miscellaneous publications (bulletins, order forms, pamphlets), 1985 - 1991 (Box 1.041, Folder 18)
  - HFA - Humane Farming Association: P2- Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1.041, Folder 19)
  - HFH - Henry Ford Hospital: P1- Published articles, 1954 (Box 1.041, Folder 20)
  - HH - Humans for Humaneness: P1- Correspondence 1980, P2- Published articles, 1982 (Box 1.041, Folder 21)
  - HHS - Haaren High School New York: P1- Publications, 1976 (Box 1.041, Folder 22)
  - HLE - Hazleton Laboratories Europe LTD.: P1- Correspondence, P2- Reports; P3- Proposal, 1975, 1977, 1978 (Box 1.042, Folder 1)
  - HIS - Human Information Services: P1- Publications, 1967, 1968, 1972, 1974 (Box 1.042, Folder 2)
  - HIS - Human Information Services: P2- Correspondence, 1968 - 1970, 1973, 1975 (Box 1.042, Folder 3)
  - HLR - Humanitarian League of Rochester: P1- Publications, P2- Correspondence, circa 1950, 1977 (Box 1.042, Folder 4)
  - HLS - Lima State Hospital: P1- Published article, 1976 (Box 1.042, Folder 5)
  - HPB - Peter Bent Brignam hospital Boston Mass.: P1- Published articles, 1976 (Box 1.042, Folder 6)
  - HPI - New York State Psychiatric Institute: P1- Published article, P2- Correspondence, 1969, 1985 (Box 1.042, Folder 7)
  - HRC - Huntington Research Center England: P1- Correspondence, P2- Publications, P3- Reports, 1973, 1976-1978 (Box 1.042, Folder 8)
  - HLG - Health research Group: P1- Reports, 1972 - 1973 (Box 1.042, Folder 9)
  - HRT - Human Research Trust: P1- Publication, 1976, 1979, 1981 (Box 1.042, Folder 10)
  - HAS - Hunt Saboteurs Association: P1- Publications, P2- Correspondence, P3- Published articles, 1976, 1979, 1985 (Box 1.042, Folder 11)
  - HSBM - Saint Bartholomew's Hospital medical College: P1- Correspondence, 1979 (Box 1.042, Folder 12)
  - HSC - Humane Society of Charlotte: P1- Miscellaneous publications, 1985, 1989 - 1990 (Box 1.042, Folder 13)
  - HSC - Humane Society of Charlotte: P2- Correspondence, P3- Published articles, 1981, 1989 -1991 (Box 1.042, Folder 14)
  - HSMC - Humane Society Marin County: P1- Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1.042, Folder 15)
  - HSRMC - Humane Society of Rochester and Monroe County: P1- Pamphlet, bulletin, P2- Published articles, 1973, 1983, 1991 (Box 1.042, Folder 16)
  - HSSN - Humane Society of Southern Nevada: P1- Pamphlet, correspondence, newsletters, 1990 - 1991 (Box 1.042, Folder 17)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P1- Pamphlets, 1975 - 1978, 1981- 1983, 1986 (Box 1.042, Folder 18)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P1- Pamphlets, 1968 - 1973 (Box 1.042, Folder 19)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P2- KIND Reports, 1975, 1979 (Box 1.042, Folder 20)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P2- National Leadership Conference, 1970 (Box 1.042, Folder 21)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P2- Booklet Twenty-five years, 1954-1979 (Box 1.042, Folder 22)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P2- Publications, 1959, 1976, 1977, 1980 (Box 1.042, Folder 23)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P3- Publications Action Alert, 1984-1990 (Box 1.042, Folder 24)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P3- Publications (bulletins), 1982-1983 (Box 1.042, Folder 25)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P3- Publications (bulletins), 1977 - 1981 (Box 1.042, Folder 26)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P4- Publications (Annual Conference programs), 1973, 1976, 1977 (Box 1.043, Folder 1)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P4- Publications (Coloring book), 1976 (Box 1.043, Folder 2)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P4- Publications (Bulletins, special reports), 1975 - 1977 (Box 1.043, Folder 3)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P4- Publications (Bulletins, order forms), 1972-1974 (Box 1.043, Folder 4)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P4- Publications (Bulletins, special reports, research), 1966, 1969 - 1971 (Box 1.043, Folder 5)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P5- Publications (Newsletters), 1981-1983, 1986-1987 (Box 1.043, Folder 6)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P5- Publications (Newsletters), 1978 - 1980 (Box 1.043, Folder 7)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P5- Publications (Newsletters), 1974-1977 (Box 1.043, Folder 8)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P5- Publications (Newsletters), 1969-1970, 1972-1973 (Box 1.043, Folder 9)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P6- Correspondence, 1981, 1983, 1989 (Box 1.043, Folder 10)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P6- Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 1.043, Folder 11)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P6- Correspondence, 1968-970, 1973 (Box 1.043, Folder 12)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P7- Published articles, 1968 - 1970, 1975, 1982 (Box 1.043, Folder 13)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P8- Reports, 1968 (Box 1.043, Folder 14)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P8- Report, 1965 (Box 1.043, Folder 15)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P9- Report, 1969 (Box 1.043, Folder 16)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P10- Reports, 1970 (Box 1.044, Folder 1)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P11- Reports, 1972 (Box 1.044, Folder 2)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P12- Reports, 1974 (Box 1.044, Folder 3)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P13- Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 1.044, Folder 4)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States: P13- Reports, 1977, 1980 (Box 1.044, Folder 5)